<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Joshua Ginsberg, aka jag</title>
    <link>https://i-am-j.ag/blog/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Joshua Ginsberg, aka jag</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://i-am-j.ag/blog/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AI needs to be designed with dignity</title>
      <link>https://i-am-j.ag/blog/posts/ai-needs-dignity/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i-am-j.ag/blog/posts/ai-needs-dignity/</guid>
      <description>Several years ago, I was visiting my brother and his family in their San Francisco home. My eldest niece was three or four years old at the time, and I was fortunate when my work included regular transcontinental business trips to be able to visit them once or twice a year. Like many of us, they owned an Amazon Echo, which my niece was allowed to request to play music. The living room was frequently filled with endless loops of the Thomas &amp;amp; Friends theme song as well as selections from the Frozen soundtrack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Desire</title>
      <link>https://i-am-j.ag/blog/posts/on-desire/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i-am-j.ag/blog/posts/on-desire/</guid>
      <description>Desire once seemed to like a simple thing to grasp and connect with. The longer I live, the more I discover how unfathomably complex desire and our relationship to it is. I&amp;rsquo;ll give you an example: dating websites.
Over a decade ago, I worked for a large dating website as a systems and network administrator. It exists no longer, but at its peak it had hundreds of thousands of daily active users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Housing</title>
      <link>https://i-am-j.ag/blog/posts/on-housing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i-am-j.ag/blog/posts/on-housing/</guid>
      <description>Asheville, North Carolina, epitomizes the dysfunction of the market for housing in America, accelerated and exacerbated by mass early retirement and shifts to telecommuting that emerged from the COVID pandemic.
Through the two years of America&amp;rsquo;s response to the pandemic, knowledge workers in more expensive locales - New York, Chicago, San Francisco, etc. - took advantage of the newfound ability to work remotely, leaning on their cost-of-living-adjusted wages and accrued home equity, to move to smaller, lower cost-of-living, higher quality-of-life cities.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
